You know what I'm saying? A lot of hard
work, a lot of uh uh grind days, man.
But you know, it's all working.
>> I never got that.
>> Cuz you don't smile much. All right. So,
which one can put a smile on your face?
>> You name you name a ton of them that
will put a smile on my face.
>> The story of Fred Smoot, which will be
told probably like 40 years from now,
right?
>> Michael B. Jordan.
>> PROBABLY CALLED SINNERS, TOO.
COMING UP ON THE GET LOUD PODCAST. WE
got not one but two special guests.
[__] is going to be here and pull up
the van. Van Jefferson signing with the
team. He's going to come in talk about
his championship experience being here
in DC.
>> Yes. And it's St. Patty's Day and we
wearing no green.
>> No. And is wearing green. She's back.
Create frenzy.
>> Yes.
>> And why you aren't leaving till you die.
Yes. The fungus among us.
>> Welcome inside the Big Bear AI Command
Center Studios. It is a GetLoud podcast
presented by SeatGeek, the official
primary ticketing partner of the
Washington Commanders. Find tickets to
Commander games and more at Segeek
Smooth. Happy St. Patty's Day, brother.
We have no green.
>> We have no green.
>> I You know what? I I hung a sweater up
and said, "You know what? I'm going to
wear this green sweater." Walk right
past it when I walk out there. Oh, you
forgot.
>> Walk right past when I walk out the
house. And you got to realize Smoot is a
Dutch Irish last name.
>> Should be really rocking a lot of green
right now, but I'm not. I'm ashamed.
>> You know what? When I went a few months
ago,
>> yeah,
>> the lovely Catherine, I getting married
in a month. It's coming up,
>> right? It's coming up. Okay. So, we went
to St. Martin, which is where we go to
vacation, right? And I had picked out a
shirt for our engagement pictures,
right? We picked it out to go with what
she was going to wear.
I forgot to pack that shirt.
>> So, you just left the shirt.
>> Oh my. And I had like a secondary shirt
and so I put that on thinking that was
the one.
>> Yeah.
>> And she was like,
>> "Yeah, you
>> shirt and I was like, "What shirt?"
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And I saw her eyes and I was like, "Oh,
>> listen. It cut
>> We worked it out. We worked it out.
>> It cut you like a knife.
>> It cut me. I was like, "I have made a
tremendous mistake."
>> But you know what we do get a chance to
do? Go out and cheers later. Right.
That's what St. Patty's Day is about.
We're not gonna let this weather right.
We Listen,
>> if another Groundhog see his shadow,
>> I'm about to lose it, Jinx.
>> Yeah.
>> Like this. How many groundhogs see they
shadow? Cuz it's been the extended
weather. I mean, just winter that I just
wasn't ready for.
>> Well, that's why we're a day late. So,
we're sorry that we're a day late cuz it
was a storm.
>> Cuz it was a storm. We couldn't even get
here. Anna just got back. What?
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. She was stuck in uh
>> I was stuck in Harrisburg Harrisburg,
Pennsylvania. They had to like what is
it called when they redirect your
flight? Yeah, they redirected my flight
and I was on the tarmac. No AC for two
hours. It was fine. I
>> also you're wearing green today.
>> I am wearing green today, but that's
because like I love St. Patrick's Day.
That
>> is worse than hearing your the pilot get
on there.
Sorry, we're about to be delayed. We're
going to sit here on the tarmac. Like
nothing just chaps me like that. Like
when I hear that I'm like, "Oh my god,
we're stuck here. We're we're not going
to leave." And then you see that line of
airplanes in front of you
>> and you know you're not leaving.
>> No, you got a long way. You know you're
not.
>> That's an O'Hare problem. I know cuz you
fly into Chicago. That is serious O'Hare
issue.
>> No. Dulles also. Yes.
>> No. That never happens to me at Dulles.
>> Now that I've said that, it will. That's
>> And And guess what? Next time you go to
Douglas, she'll be stuck there.
>> The best experience I had with a flight
attendant once, it was early. You ever
flown Spirit? Yeah. Yeah. It's Yeah.
It's like it's like everything.
Everything. And this it was early.
Everybody was in a bad mood cuz you
think you're getting a good deal and
then you turn the page on a magazine
they charge you for it. Like it's
terrible.
>> Yeah. Your bag, every bag, everything.
>> And this guy is giving the announcements
over the loudspeaker and he says,
"Before you ask, we don't have Wi-Fi,
but if we did, you bet your ass we're
going to charge you for it." So I
thought it was funny, right? So we're
laughing, right? Everyone else is tired.
So he loved that we laughed at the joke.
So at about 6:37, he rolls by and he's
got two small bottles of vodka. He goes,
"Here you go."
>> Yeah.
>> I was like, "Oh, about that. Thank you,
man. Appreciate that."
>> Because you you laughed at his grander.
Nobody else did cuz everybody else like,
"Yeah, you are charging us for
everything."
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's part of it.
>> I was like, it was funny. Hey, send us
your voicemails, email us, like and
subscribe, all the good stuff.
7037267419.
7037267419
or you can email us as usual
washingtonget loudgmail.com and it's
coming up. People want to challenge you
the draft guru.
>> I am the draft
>> yes to the draft.
>> Yeah.
>> And now that Adam Peters has just made
it unpredictable on who we going to
draft because of what we did in free
agency. I always tell people it's a
cause and effect because of what happens
in free agency. It affects the draft.
All right. And now that we have filled
in all of these slots, now everybody's
wondering what is Washington going to do
at seven. Are they going to hit the
reverse on that thing and bag back and
let somebody else trade up? Are they
going to stay put and take this guy or
this guy? And as I listen to radio talk,
I've heard 30 names we should take.
>> Oh god.
>> I've heard all kind of names. All right.
And it's it's fun. Like that's one thing
about the draft to me is fun. Not only
because we're going to add a new talent
to the team, but also we don't know and
everybody thinks they know who we're
going to get and who we're going to
draft and we just do not know. So I'm
ready to face everybody on this
challenge of who, what, and when because
everybody's falling in love with Sunonny
Styles. He's the new model in the room.
He's the guy who already had the talent,
but then he showed out at the underwear
Olympics.
>> Yes, he did. And then you got the New
York Giants sitting there at five. All
right. With Harbaugh right there, a guy
that didn't had that middle linebacker
his whole career. All right. Does he
take him? Does he say no? I going to get
Jackson Dart, a Jeremiah Love. All
right. Like, so it's just so much
>> Yeah.
>> drama in the top 10 right now. The only
spot that is no drama is number one.
>> Yeah,
>> the Raiders have to go Mendoza. Like if
they don't go Mendoza, that's just them
being the Raiders.
>> Yeah, they will. They will. They have
to. They have. They should fold as a
franchise. They don't take him.
>> They're going to take Mendoza. But
everything after that is up because
nobody know what the Jets are going to
do. Because here go the thing about RL
Ree.
>> For as freaky as he is as an athlete,
>> we ain't seen him pass rush the whole
season, right? We ain't like like I
always say this. If I'm going to take
somebody in the top 10, I need to know
what you do well and I need to see you
do it over and over and over again. All
right. Well, this the only thing about
RL Ree for what we going to ask you to
do in the league cuz he's he's labeled
as a edge.
>> Mhm.
>> I didn't see you pass rush a lot.
>> Do you run a 44? Yeah, you do.
>> Yeah.
>> Are you 6'5? Yes.
>> You look good getting off the bus. But
if you're the Jets
>> Mhm. Do you not take David Bailey, a guy
that's been there, done that showed you
I'm the best pass rusher in the draft.
>> Also, you know what's fascinating too is
how each year, like two years ago when
Jane came out with Caleb Williams and
Fenix, all those guys,
>> credible draft class at quarterback,
right?
>> Yeah. At quarterback. This year it's
Mendoza.
>> Oh,
>> and then like that's I mean there
Simpson, but
>> you got Tai Simpson right there,
>> right? But for the most part, it's not a
deep class at all.
>> Not not at quarterback. But then in o
other years like this one, receiver is
deep edge. There's a lot of players.
>> Well, here goes some intriguing things
about the quarterback position. You got
the consensus number one.
>> Then you got Ty Simpson that that's like
should we or should we not? Then you got
a Tayen Green from from Arkansas that's
6'5 that runs a 4340
>> athletic freak
>> that people are wondering could I go put
him in Detroit and let him sit
behind a quarterback like that or is it
a is it a Rams later pick him behind
Stafford let him sit. So it's some it's
some guys in this draft. The question
is, if it's a quarterback, are you going
to be patient with him or are you gonna
jump it and go get you a Ty Simpson or
Carson Beck?
>> Oh man, like Carson Beck, like did he
just make your stomach turn?
>> Isn't it crazy too how if you look at
the totality of his career? He's a very
good quarterback, but in cre in key
moments.
>> All right. All right.
>> Is that fair? I mean, I feel like we saw
the national you.
>> Okay.
>> I'm not saying he this player. I'm not
saying he gonna be this player,
>> okay?
>> I'm saying,
do you remember when Tom Brady came out?
>> Oh, don't do this.
>> I'm just All right. Drew Henson.
>> Okay.
>> And Tom Brady shared time at Michigan
his senior year.
>> That's very true.
>> All right. MICHIGAN WON A LOT OF GAMES.
>> YEAH.
>> All right. But we WEREN'T SURE WHO TOM
WAS.
>> I got the same effect with Carson Beck.
Like you've played in tons of big games.
I've seen you come up short. I've seen
you come up being. I don't know who you
are.
>> Okay, that's fair because I know it's
easy to latch on to a narrative, latch
on to a storyline and say, "Oh, this is
who you are. This is who you are."
>> I don't want to do that with
>> And that's fair, especially with a
college player because
>> as much as Yes, there were times in key
moments where he threw late in games
interceptions, there were times when he
did come through as well.
>> No, he came through at Georgia. Like, it
was time that he he did. So he's he's
one of those guys where I'm like I do
not know who you are. Think about it. If
you're Drew Drew Aller Aller,
>> okay,
>> HE WAS SLOTTED TO BE THE FIRST
QUARTERBACK TAKEN.
>> If he come out last year, HE PROBABLY
WOULD HAVE BEEN.
>> YES. SO IF YOU'RE SITTING AT HOME AND
YOU'RE Pixsburg like, do I need to get
another guy to put on this bench and see
can I mold him into what I want him to
be?
>> That's Drew Holla. You you you looking
and you're saying he can be a future
starter in this league. Garrett Nusamire
from uh LSU can wing it.
>> He can
>> he can wing it. Got hurt at the end of
the year. Who are you?
>> Like so the quarterback draft question
mark.
>> Yeah.
>> Pass rush. No question mark in this
draft. It's a pass rushers delight. It's
a quarterback's delight. It's guys out
here that starters and I'm talking about
to the 60th or 70th pick. So it's guy
it's some dudes out here. I feel like if
you started a band, it'd be like
quarterback's delight.
>> Cornerback's delight.
>> Like dessert.
>> Even at tight end, everybody talking
about Sadique. Eli Sty from Vanderbilt.
>> Yeah.
>> Bowler. Like he really killed
>> I think he played quarterback at one
time when he was playing quarterback.
And you talking about 43 inch vertical.
You're talking about a guy that ran a
4440. Like it's some studs in this
draft. This draft right here is one of
those drafts what I call retire me
draft. This is the draft that pushes old
guys out
>> like because every every draft year
ain't a good draft.
>> That's right.
>> This is a good draft that's gonna push
some old veterans to the pasture. Come
on where I'm at. Come on over here.
We're over in the pasture.
>> Come on down.
Retirement don't Hey, retirement. The
one thing about it in the league, we
don't choose it. It chooses us. Because
you would never retire if it's up to us.
We think we can play forever. I'm fresh.
Just out there getting burnt at 40, just
just look terrible. And I'm like, I
still got it.
>> No, you don't.
>> Let me ask you this because you seem to
take it easy.
>> Yeah.
>> But when you're a competitor like you
are, like guys in the NFL are,
>> it has to hurt when it finally hits you
>> that it's over.
>> It's over. What was it like when it
finally hit you?
>> It was like I rolled over one morning.
Uhhuh.
>> And my brain told my body to get out the
bed, but my body didn't listen.
And I was still laying in the bed. And
that's when I was like, this might be
the end of the road.
>> Is that right?
>> Because
my body ain't responding to my mind no
more. Like, so is it my body saying it's
time? Cuz my mind I can do it forever,
but my body is telling me now whatever's
left, save it for yourself.
>> So yes, it's hard. And I can promise you
my first year away from football, I did
not watch football jinx. I did not watch
pro. The only thing I watched was
college.
>> Did you need a break or did it hurt too
much?
>> It hurt. Yeah.
>> It hurt to watch people that I just was
playing against still playing.
>> Get that
>> cuz if he can still do it, I can still
do it. And that's the mindset.
>> Yeah. Sure.
>> And by watching these dudes, I'm like,
turn the TV. I'm gonna watch something
else because it just didn't feel right
for me to watch a pro game and I wasn't
even getting ready to play a team uh
playing a team. Yeah. And it felt
awkward and it felt not right. So yeah,
it hurts that first year just it hurts
mentally, it hurts physically. It hurts
everything. The only thing that feels
good that first year away from football
is your body.
>> I get that.
>> Yeah. But personally, yeah, mentally you
hurt. You hurt as a person. Well, AP
went out, got some dudes who are not
ready to be put out to pasture just yet.
They're in their prime.
>> They're in their prime. It ain't nothing
like hearing that when you're athlete.
You're in your prime. You're like,
"Yeah,
>> forever."
>> That's me. I am in my prime.
>> Yeah.
>> Odaf Ooway Clayon Chson. We're talking
about the edge position.
>> Oh, so long on the defensive line.
>> Both of them so long. Yeah.
>> Like that's what I like about it. So
long. You want them long fast edges. And
what I like about it, they didn't just
go say, "You know what? We fa to go get
this one guy, this Lawrence Taylor. We
finn to go get guys
>> cuz if you remember with coach Quinn
in in Seattle, it wasn't just one guy
that that passed. It was dudes in
Seattle showed you this year.
>> I was just going to say look at the
Super Bowl was just like one cat after
another. And that's what you want. All
right. You want to relentlessly continue
to send guys at you. And that's what I
think
>> we put together right here. When you
look at the guys that they got. Keep
going down the list.
>> How about an old friend? Yeah. Tim
Settle.
>> Tim Settles. He going to think about
>> just a big plug in the middle.
>> He going to think about me and Tim.
>> Okay.
>> I was just with Tim months ago when he
when he uh left Houston, came back cuz
Tim is my my kid's cousin.
>> Oh, okay. I know. So we basically
family.
>> Like my kids cousin is Tim Ser. So like
I told them, y'all just saw TWO PROS.
Y'ALL GOT NO EXCUSES. HUH? YOU GOT A pro
on your mama's side. You got a pro, your
daddy. All right. I don't want to HEAR
NO EXCUSES ABOUT YOU CAN'T MAKE IT to
the league. All right. It's in your
blood.
>> It's in your DNA.
>> It's in your blood. So me and Tim
family.
>> But you know what? This is a guy who if
you want a run, a pure run stopper, I
mean, this is your guy right there. Just
take on guys.
>> Put him in the middle of the line and
let him loose. That's that's what you
want. He going to keep Leo Chanel clean.
He going to keep Frankie Luvu clean.
See, that go the sacrifice of a D line.
>> Ray Lewis all that time in in uh the
Ravens in Baltimore, he had Sarah Gusa,
he had all them big boys in front of
him. Their job was to keep the the the
center the guards off of him so he can
run sideline to sideline. Tim Settle is
going to do the same.
>> That's a really good point because and
it's a defensive strategy too, right? Do
you turn your defensive lineman loose or
do you have them just plug up the middle
and that way your linebackers can get
loose and beggressive?
>> The thing about it, you have them plug
on rundowns, you let them loose on
passdowns. There go the thing about it.
Like the one thing I don't like
defensive coordinators to do to my D
tackles and my DNS, I don't want to have
them two gapping all the time cuz now
when they come off the ball, first thing
they going to do is this and this.
>> So now they're looking to respond
instead of shooting the gap. Okay?
>> I want them shooting the gap at all
times and we'll we'll clean the rest up
on the back end, right?
>> But I want you to to disturb the play.
And the only way you can disturb the
play if if you shooting the gap. But I
don't need you uh reading and reacting
cuz if you reading and reacting, these
running backs too good. Yeah. So, no, I
want them shooting together. I want
chaos. Organized chaos. You ever seen a
ant bed? Have you ever dropped a piece
of candy in ant bed? They want organized
chaos. We all got a job to do and we all
going to go get our little piece.
>> Mhm.
>> That's what it's about.
>> A lot of free agent acquisitions. Let's
Let's stay on the defensive offensive
side. You mentioned him. Chanel. Leo
Chanel. Is he just the biggest man you
ever seen in your life?
>> This cat is rocked up. He's rocked up
and he's hyper aggressive. And you know,
Spags can coach defense and he was
saying this is a guy who played five
different positions for us in Kansas
City. So, you can move him anywhere. And
he's he is going to be aggressive.
>> He can rush off the edge. He can play in
space. He can cover tight ends. He can
run sideline to sideline.
He is a specimen.
>> He looks like a pro wrestler.
>> Yes. He look like Brock Lesnar. Like
listen to me.
>> When I was at Minnesota, Brock Lesnar
was trying out for the team.
>> Oh, I forgot about that. And every time
I look down there at the defensive line,
he down there fighting.
He down there wrestling
uh big big uh McKini
>> to the ground. I'm like, WHAT IS HE
DOING? Like yes, I was on a team with a
wrestler. Oh my god, I'VE FORGOTTEN
ABOUT THAT.
>> YES, Brock Lesnar was a Minnesota Viking
for a while.
>> For a while.
>> It's a couple of actors that's been ex
football players that turn to actors cuz
we have
>> Terry Cruz.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Terry Cruz play here with
with Ken and a lot of other guys. So,
yeah, it's it's these guys that went on
to do other things. Yeah.
>> That started in the NFL. So, they're
telling me I got a chance to be a
comedian.
>> A Meek Robertson.
>> Yes. And we're going to ask B Mitch
about Aek, but this is a guy who's
played for the Raiders, played for the
Lions, and he's not the biggest guy, but
man, you talk about a guy who's going to
fight you and be physically is the word
you want to say when you talk about Aek.
Feisty. And everything that he's earned
in this league, he had to earn it. He's
been given nothing. All right. He's been
a guy that they've been asked to put on
the island with Justin Jefferson. He
don't turn it down. He's a guy that been
asked to check DJ Moore solo. He don't
turn it down. He's a guy that he's
basically a AP guy.
>> I'm a guy that whatever you give me, I'm
going to take it and make it more. Like
he's that guy. And he's a guy that you
ain't going to appreciate him until he
starts to play. His name won't just ring
off the thing with you. Like when he
starts to play, then you'll be like, "Oh
yeah, I appreciate this guy." He's a guy
that can make stuff happen. And every
time he gets out there, he makes stuff
happen. Uh he's a guy like Ryan Clark.
>> Okay. Like people couldn't really
appreciate what Ryan Clark brought to
the table until you watch Ryan Clark
play. Because if you just say the name
Ryan Clark, it wasn't going to just blow
you out, blow you up. It was going to be
watch Ryan Clark play. And now I
appreciate what he brings to the table.
>> Yeah. And plus fellow football players
will notice that and say
>> all your football like football players
know the football player side of the
football.
>> Right. Yeah.
>> And Robinson is a guy too kind of like
Mikey Sanders still who played inside
and out. I know he came out of college
in the slot, but Robinson can play
inside and out as well.
>> Yeah. And that's what you want.
Versatility. All of these guys
versatile. And that's what you want. You
want all right, one man go down. We
don't need to be searching on the street
to find somebody to fill a gap when we
got other people that could just say,
you know what, I could do that for the
next three weeks. That's fine with me.
>> Nick Cross, this is one of those sneaky
really good signings because if you talk
about being aggressive and a guy that's
going to hit you and wrap you up, yes,
it's him.
>> Welcome home. All right, Marilyn Turpp.
I always woring about them Turpps. All
right. We got two Turpps.
>> All right. Oh, that's right. Him and Ch.
Yeah. They also played together. So,
most definitely. Welcome home. And I can
only wonder how that feels cuz you know
Mississippi State, our closest pro team
is Tennessee, the Titans. So, we ain't
really got that presence hovering over
us. But, I can only wonder with Nick and
Chig watching Washington football the
whole time while they in college. And
I'm sure at one point they could see
theyel rocking this uniform and now they
get a chance to not only play and
represent for the city, but I'm sure
it's some how should I say some internal
things where I feel like, yeah, this is
where I should be. This is who I should
be, where I should be. And like you
said,
>> well-rounded safety right there. He does
everything well. And
>> his sure tackling is what I do love.
Like the one thing we was not good at
last year was tackling in the defensive
back field.
>> I started to say you don't want guys to
get in the secondary, but if they do,
>> we need them on the ground, right? We
that was our we the last line of defense
back there in the defensive back field.
If we don't get them down, they don't go
down. And that's what we was always
taught. If we don't get them down, just
London used to always say, just give us
another chance to make a play. All
right? And if y'all can get them to the
ground, we got another chance to go make
a play. And this what made us good. How
about on the offensive side? Let's start
with Rashad White. Well,
>> reunited with his brother and his
brother. Feels so good.
>> Hey, listen. Rashad White, one of the
best better receivers out the back field
when it comes to running backs. And he's
a guy, he a three down back. He's a guy
that can stay on the field the entire
time. And he's a guy that didn't played
with Jaden before. So they they they
like it's a lot of cross, how should I
say, connections?
>> They really are though. Yeah. Yeah. Like
it's a lot of like guys like even though
they're new to the team, they not really
new to a lot of people in the locker
room,
>> right?
>> So that makes it easier for people to
step right in and pick up where they
left off at. All right. So I think with
him, he just one of them guys that I I
can't wait to see him in totality,
right?
>> Like like what's going to be his niche?
Because all I think I still think it's
Bill's backfield.
>> Yeah, I think it is too. I still think
>> it gives them an option particularly in
the passing game like you were saying.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But in the passing game, I
think that's where Rashad White has a
step on on Bill and that's with pass
catching
>> all on oneear deal. So I know it's easy
to say, oh, they got a loaded backfield.
They wouldn't go after Jeremiah Love.
That's not TRUE AT ALL.
>> NO, NO. FIRST OF ALL, EVERYBODY'S
eligible to be A WASHINGTON COMMANDER.
LIKE SITTING AT SEVEN, THE ONLY PERSON
that's legitely not eligible is Mendoza.
>> Like that's the only guy that's not
legitely have a chance to beat Well, I
say Mendoza are some of the tackles. We
don't need them. We don't need the
tackles. So, everybody else has a legit
chance to be a Washington commander.
>> No, you're right about that. And plus, I
mean, we'll talk about the draft as it
gets closer, too. I feel like Love is
one of those
>> running back is always iffy, but man,
the closer we get to the draft, it's
going to be hard for a lot of teams to
pass up on him.
>> I just think he I always look I I told
you I feel like it's four or five what
we call genetically freaks in this
draft.
>> I just want one of them.
>> Yeah,
>> So, at the end of our free agent
segment,
>> Yeah. You might have been wondering,
what about Van Jefferson?
>> What about him?
>> That's because we got the man right here
in studio. How you doing, man?
>> How you doing?
>> Good. Thanks for being with us. And and
what's it been like so far coming in
here, meeting everybody and making the
transition.
>> Yeah, it's been great. Um, everybody's
been so welcoming. Um, excited to be a
part of the organization, man. It's
excited to be a part of this uh regime
and this organization.
>> Well, Van, as a quarterback, man, the
reason I played quarterback because not
because of the hands, cuz the hands
soft. I play quarterback cuz I want to
control my own destiny. And one thing
about wide receivers, y'all kind of are
prisoners to the quarterback position,
like who is your quarterback? So, how
does it feel to have Jaden as your
quarterback now? That's that's different
than what you had.
>> Yeah, man. Excited to to have him my
quarterback, man. Excited. Uh I think um
just seeing him, you know, from afar,
you know, appreciating his game and how
he commands his huddle, commands the
team, and how he can just can take
control of a game, man. I'm excited to
be a part of that, and excited to work
with him. Are you excited the fact that
he's one of those guys once he gets out
the the pocket, it's not the first route
you ran that you can really get loose on
us as a corner, it's the second route,
>> right? Exactly. Yeah. Hey, we call that
scramble drill. Scramble drill. So, you
know, uh just keep your head on the
silver, man. Make it make yourself
available for the quarterback.
>> Yep.
>> And what are your thoughts on the the
receiving room, particularly Terry, of
course, one of the best in the league,
and now you're going to make that
receiving room even better.
>> Yeah. Um Terry is one of one, you know,
um
>> uh his game speaks for himself, you
know. Um, he's deservedly, you know, one
of the top guys to get paid and, um,
someone I can learn from when I'm here
and, you know, um, get to know him more
and trailing. I was with trailing in
Tennessee. So, I'm excited. Yeah.
Excited to be back with him and, um, you
know, he's a he's a freak of nature,
too, as well. You know what I'm saying?
So, to play with him and Luke McCaffrey
and, um, you know, just learning from
those guys and, you know, bringing my
expertise to the game and, you know, but
also, you know, we're all just, you
know, on one accord and just, you know,
playing as one. How does it feel to to
see your guy Trey Lun be here and him
having a just a breath of fresh air
being here compared to when he was at
Tennessee?
>> Right. Sometimes you need that, you
know. Sometimes you need that. You know,
he probably needed a fresh air and um
you know, he came look was like he came
in and just fit in right away. You know,
I remember watching that Sunday night
game where he had that one. Yeah.
Onehanded catch, man. So, I was so
excited for him, you know, cuz all the
ups and downs that he had and for him to
have a big moment like that, man, and I
know it's only going to turn on good for
this upcoming season for him. One thing
we've noticed with some of the free
agents coming in is that a lot of them
have championship experience. You have
that championship experience. So,
>> how can you use that experience to lead
other guys who want to get to the
pinnacle? You've been there.
>> Yeah. Uh I mean, it's hard to get to the
pinnacle. It's hard. You know what I'm
saying? A lot of hard work, a lot of uh
>> uh grind days, man. But, you know, it's
all worth it.
>> I never got there.
>> It's all worth it, man. It's all worth
it. So, you know, if you just put the
work in, man, put your mind to it, you
know. Um got to have a lot of guys that
buy in. Um man, anything can happen. So,
you know, um but you don't you just it's
step by step. Step step be where your
feet are and you know um it'll happen.
>> Have you got time to uh talk to any
other the other free agents that came to
the team? Have you have time to sit down
with any of them and see where they head
at and why they chose the same place you
chose?
>> Uh no sir, I haven't but um you know
when they get inward looking forward to
it. Yes, sir. Yeah, I cuz I've been part
of like a free agent group when I went
to Minnesota and we had a big old group
and the first thing we did was all right
if it's this many of us coming in how
about we sit and go have some dinner and
get and kind of get to know each other.
>> Yeah, we need to do that. We need to do
that. Yeah.
>> Don't worry. I'm going to set y'all up
at DC Prime. Okay, cool. I'm going to
make sure y'all got all the stuff you
need, all the fixings you need.
>> And you know, you come into a situation
where, and this happens to every player,
like are they in a position to succeed,
right? And you're a guy who comes in and
you feel a need, which is this offense
needs someone who can stretch the
>> field.
Yeah. Um, you know,
>> I'm just going to do what the officer
tells me to do. You know what I'm
saying? I'm going to be a team player.
You know what I'm saying? Um, whatever
my role is, I'm going to be the best at
their role. You know what I'm saying?
Um, not bigger than the team. So, at the
end of the day, just coming in learning,
you know, um, being the stewards of the
game and, you know, um, learning from
others on the field, too. And, um, so,
you know, whatever that role is, I'm
going to be the best at it. Now, I want
to burst our view because I as an ex
player, we all watch each other. We all
watch each other team.
>> Yeah.
>> I want you to take I want to take you
back two years ago when Jaden was a
rookie and Washington was catching fire
as you were sitting over there looking
from afar. What was you thinking about
what's going on in Washington right now?
>> Man, I'm just thinking about they they
find a franchise quarterback for sure.
>> They got to do.
>> Yeah, they got the dude. They got the
dude. I mean, I remember plays DeAndre
Brown catching the post down the middle.
I remember Terry Mclo on the screen
taking it all the way. So against
Detroit against Detroit. Yeah. So I
remember all those plays, man. And just
seeing it from afar, you just admire,
you know, how those guys work and how
great of a quarterback Jay Daniels is
going to be. And um, you know, man, I'm
excited to be a part of it.
>> Most definitely.
>> What's it like to have a fresh start and
you bounce around a little bit, but
clearly you've had a lot of success in
the NFL. So at the same time, you have
that veteran experience, but also you
want to be in a place where you can show
what you can do.
>> Yeah, of course. You know, um,
obviously, you know, everyone's goal is
to stay with one team, you know, and to
be with the team the longest, but
sometimes it doesn't work out that way.
>> No, we get our heart.
>> Exactly.
>> I tell people all the time, don't worry
about one team. Worry about who the one
team that wants. Exactly.
>> That's all it's about.
>> You only need one. So, you know, um,
just coming in and having that veteran
experience and, uh, playing with guys,
you know, um, I can teach and like I
said, learn from too as well. So, I'm
just excited for the opportunity.
>> Yeah.
>> Hey, I got one more thing I can say.
Look, Mississippi State,
>> don't you? I really I He's a Texas dude.
>> Okay.
>> We did.
>> I mean, I was like, we got all
>> SEC to the SEC.
>> He knew. He knew.
>> But I don't know. Florida been down.
>> We've been down. I know. FLORIDA BEEN
DOWN. NOW, SPEAKING FROM Mississippi
State Bulldog, now that we got a
quarterback, now that we starting to
turn the page, what's going on in
Florida? Are y'all going to take that
state back? That's just Miami is the
claim right now.
>> Nah, nah. We going to take the state
back. We got a new head coach. We got
some new some new fresh faces. Man, we
we back and we back and rolling right
now. We back losing that recruiting
battle that y'all used to win.
>> Not no more. Not no more. Not no more.
We going to be good. We going to be
good.
>> I'm just saying used to dominate the
state of Florida. It used to be your
thing. And I'll never forget I was in
high school. Uh Steve Spurer came to
Mississippi to recruit my middle
linebacker. He signed my middle
linebacker. And I told him as I was
sitting on the curb, I said, "You don't
see number one on that field." And he
just smiled there. I said, "Either you
going to have to play against me or you
going to have to play with me. You
choose." Yeah. He did not recruit me. So
when I got a chance to play against
Spuria, we blew y'all out about that.
>> You made a mistake with that one. You
made a mistake.
>> He made a mistake with that one.
>> I always love when you talk NFL with
guys and they get excited, but then you
ask about the college and sometimes you
get even more excited. You know what I
mean?
>> Cuz college is who we are. Like college
is that go the story being told right
there. the pro is is almost the end
game, but the story I mean the story is
college and but see I don't know like
cuz I tell my kid I got a son that's
coming out he's a wide receiver he he
going to be pretty good
>> but I told him man I really want you to
go to one school like I know all these
guys going to different schools but I
want you to have a true alumni base cuz
if you go to three schools who is your
alumni base isn't the last school you
went to
>> yeah that nil something crazy right now
didn't it change the game
>> yeah it changed the game
>> let me ask you this
>> if you was in NIA right now coming out
Van Jeff where would you where you think
the money would have took you cuz it
ain't about loyalty no more
>> man that money hey that money talk
>> you ain't turn it down no went to
college
for real
>> yeah it's different now
>> it's different now it's different now
but I mean I had a great college
experience I mean being at University of
Florida but I I was a two college kid
too I went to miss and then I
transferred to uh you didn't uh I did so
>> you right you did go Why you selling
your sold me?
>> Well, I I I I love Hugh Fes. Hugh Freeze
was my was a great coach and he was a
great recruiter. So, I chose Hugh
Freeze, not the school. You know what
I'm saying? So, but then when I transfer
to Florida, I chose the school.
>> And um but Florida was one of the best
college experience I ever had, man. I
still got best friends to this day that
I still talk to. Ain't nothing like
being on campus, riding scooters around
campus, man. Going to class with your
dogs, y'all just having fun, man. Stuff
like that. You know what I'm saying?
>> Games are like that.
>> Yeah. It's like that. It's like that.
It's like that. It's like that. Yeah.
So,
>> but man, college is one of the best
experience for sure.
>> Yeah. That's what's up.
>> Well, man, thanks for being with us and
welcome to DC. Thank you,
>> man. Welcome to the squad, baby. Welcome
to the family.
>> I appreciate you.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Let's continue talking about NFL free
agency, specifically who the commanders
brought in. And for that, we bring in
the man who has the second most
all-purpose yards in NFL history, Brian
Mitchell. You know, B Mitch. How you
doing, B Mitch?
>> I'm good, man. What's happening? How
y'all doing?
>> You looking young over there, brother.
You looking You finally found the youth
and didn't tell nobody.
>> Hey, man. I was that pellet is my youth
every morning 15 miles this morning but
made a lot.
>> So when you look at this free agent
class that Washington brought in how
would you rate it overall and why?
>> Well I think they did an outstanding
job. You know uh they needed help on
defense and most of the signings were on
the defensive side of the football and
then when you look at what they did
offensively they got guys in key
positions. You got a tight end intrigue.
Okay. You got some running backs to come
in there and help out out the back field
as well. Uh then you bring back Marcus
Mariota which I think was an
unbelievable move because many people
felt he would get a chance to leave but
him coming back you know that that kind
of solidifies having that backup. I
think that's as important as anything
else. You also the things they did with
signing some of their own guys bringing
Chris Paul back you know making sure you
get Tonsel back. They touched a lot of
bases this year. uh and they missed on
some last year, but this year I think
they've hit and I think the guys are
going to go out there and perform and
produce for them.
>> I agree with you, B miss, but when I get
to really looking at this list, I I I
look a edge deeper and I look and I see
K uh Chaison just played in the Super
Bowl. I see Tim Settle just played in
the playoffs. I see uh Adaf.
The Chargers was right there at it. And
I'm looking at guys that been there and
done that. Do you think that uh AP had a
pedigree that he was looking at when he
he he went got these free agents?
Because Leo Chanel has played in two
Super Bowls, one two Super Bowl. These
guys been there and done that. B Mitch,
>> well, he he has guys that are you like
he wanted to get younger. He wanted to
get faster. He did that, but he got
younger and faster. Also, he got
experience. A lot of these guys have
played in the playoffs, as you just
stated. Leo Chanel, you look at a guy
who's been to two Super Bowls. He was
teammates with Alec Grey and Wy, you
know. Uh when you start bringing in the
youthful guys with that experience, it
it makes your team take a jump, you
know. And I know people always talk
about you want to get younger, you wanna
you want to have experience, but you got
to have a delicate balance of what that
is. And now you bring some guys in that
are like these guys are starting to hit
their stride. They're ascending, but
they are still have a lot to go. And I
think, you know, we we've so many times
went out there and got guys that had
done it already in the league for years,
and now they were on the down slope. No,
we got guys on the ups slope now and I
think that should work out for us.
>> So, [__] when they brought in the guys
that they did particularly at Edge, do
you think that means they go away from
Edge in the draft?
>> No. You know, I I really believe what
they've done, they've set themselves up
now to where they can go anywhere they
choose to go,
>> anywhere.
>> I think when you start looking at play
best player available now, you can do
that. They're not forced to go anywhere.
They got they got help at running back.
They got help at uh defensive back and
safety. They got help on the edge. They
bought their offensive lineman back. So
now whoever falls in your lap, you know,
if you have that guy on your board
that's the number one guy, you can go
out there and get him. So, and I love
that fact that, you know, we're now now
aren't pressed to say we got to get a
certain position. No, you add a player
that's going to come in here off the bat
and make uh make some make an impact for
you.
>> Yeah, B Mitch, I'm with you on that one.
Especially when like cuz you know I love
that draft now and right now the way we
to set oursel up I got people you know
when I'm looking at uh some people's uh
board I'm seeing Jeremiah Love I'm
seeing uh uh uh Sadiq I'm seeing uh
Sunonny Styles I'm seeing like four five
different uh people that dropped to us
and I think when he went got this and
reinforced this defensive front all
right then you went got Leo Chenel at
the linebacker then you went get Nick
Cross at the defensive back then you go
get Rashad White and the rest of those
uh running backs You're saying right now
we're taking best player available. Do
you agree with me?
>> I agree with that 100%. And I think
that's the position you want to be in.
You know, you don't want to go into the
draft saying I have to get a certain
person and then all of a sudden somebody
realize that's what you're trying to do.
They take him from you and then you now
you're shook. But now they're in a
position where we they can grab a multip
multitude of guys from different
positions and still be able to hit a
home run. [__] who's the most
underrated guy that they signed that
they brought in where you think, you
know, maybe he's not getting talked
about like the other dudes, but this guy
could play.
>> I'm going to go with A Meek Robinson to
be totally honest with you. Listen, he
he people talk trash about him, but
>> I don't normally sit at home and watch
whole football games. I'm only watch
whole football games when I'm working
with the team, and I sat home and I
watched Detroit play last year against
uh against Minnesota. And I know Justin
Jefferson is a straight dog. And Amique
Robinson beat his ass all over the
football field. I'm telling you, when
you follow Justin Jefferson and you're
with him, you have to be with him manto
man all day and you have that much of an
impact and output against him, you're a
good football player. You know that that
young man not only is a great cover guy,
he's a competitor. Also, he will hit you
and he's a he's a sure tackler. That's
something that we needed. Also, we talk
about a lot of different things on the
football team. And I think when we look
defensively, they didn't have a lot of
sure tackling going on last year. So,
anybody who can get to come in there and
be a sure tackler is a great guy for me.
So, I think he's one of those under uh
you know, one of those guy people not
talking about as much, but he's going to
have a major impact for us.
>> I'm gonna have to go. I'm gonna have to
say at the tight end position. I'm g
have to say at the tight end position.
You got a guy
>> I think he's underweighted though. Uh
Fred, I think people know what he can
do.
>> Yeah, I I know it. But but but like you
said,
>> I feel like he never reached his peak at
Tennessee. I feel like he still has room
to reach his peak and his yards after
the catch. His ability to make people
miss, his ability to get up the scene,
his ability like No, no, not ability.
His willingness to block, I think just
says everything when you talking about a
tight end
>> in Tennessee. He had you throwing him
the football.
>> Yeah.
His potential. Now he's gonna have
somebody getting the ball to him. This
kid is gonna be something special, man.
He catches the ball. He's unbelievable
after the catch. So that's the thing I'm
gonna like about it. I think now we have
a tight end who can stretch the field.
Yeah.
>> And I think when that tight end can
stretch that field, safeties can't come
down in the box. They got to be
concerned about stuff over the top. Now
you open it up for your outside guys and
your running game. And you know, B
Mitch, I know he's not a free agent, but
I love the way they they started this
whole process, which is locking down
Larry Tonsel because if you're going to
build your team out, make sure you
extend the rock on that offensive line.
>> Oh, yeah, man. I think that's like when
you look at one of the best in the
league at the left tackle position. And
then when you listen to every offensive
lineman on this team to a man, they
always talk about what Larry has done,
how he's come here, changed their
mindset, he's been a leader for them,
you know, talking about the culture that
is being built, they got it done
immediately. And I think a lot of people
now you look at all the people coming in
here. A lot of that happens because they
say, "Oh, they take care of their own
guys. I'll go check them out."
>> Yep. Yep. You're right about that. And
as a guy that was welcome back, you
know, I left home and I came back home
myself. I have to give some love to Tim
Settles. All right. What he's did at the
Texas what he's he solidified himself as
one of these guys. I I'm a winning
DTackle on a winning team. How do you
feel about the guys that's coming back
for their second stint as as a
Washington player?
>> Well, I like the fact that Tim is coming
back as a more experienced player. You
the thing about we had him on the radio
show and he asked me know what are you
going to do? He said, "I'm be right
there in the middle." You know, not
everybody want to be that big guy in the
middle who has to take on blocks to make
sure the people are going to be good. He
understands that's that's going to be
his role. I know you touched on this a
little bit, B Mitch, but how much does
it help a team when you have guys who
have won Super Bowls or been to that
point come in as a part of your team? I
feel like that just kind of builds that
expectation and it helps these guys lead
other dudes who are in the locker room
as well.
>> Easy to trust a guy that been there.
>> Hey, that's that's the thing about it. F
is absolutely right. They're going to
listen to them because they've been
there. And if those guys say do
something, the guys are going to do it.
It was like when I got here in 1990,
hell, all these guys had been to a Super
Bowl, had won two of them already. And
when those guys said do something, I
didn't question anything. I did what
they said. And like we always talk about
you have to learn how to win. You know
what? You can learn how to lose too. So
if you're losing game, you learn how to
lose. But those guys come in here with
that experience of how to not worry
about thing, not let things get too big.
Treat every game like a regular game.
And when you have your teammates telling
you that day in and day out, it becomes
a part of your like like this a second
nature to you. And when you got that,
everything goes well. You know, too many
times when you're trying to get there,
you put too much emphasis on certain
games. And when you put pressure on
yourself, hey, most time you put too
much pressure, you can't live up to it.
>> B Mitch. All right. I feel like we we we
just killed free agency. What's the
icing on the cake? Who if you could name
one player, is it Kenyan Sadique, the
tight end from Oregon? Is it Jeremiah
Love? Is it Sunny Styles? Is it Orville
Reese? Like if if if it's a perfect
draft day for B Mitch, who name gets
called with the number seven pick in
this year's draft that's really just
going to set you off and put a smile ON
YOU BECAUSE YOU DON'T SMILE MUCH. ALL
RIGHT. SO, WHICH one can put a smile on
your face? You name you name a ton of
them that will put a smile on my face.
And I I think that's the thing about it
where I don't have to be sitting here
like stressing over them getting one
particular person.
>> There's five to seven guys that they can
get and I'm gonna be exactly happy with
it because right now this we went into
this off season like needing a lot and
then Adam went to work. Now you just
need somebody that's going to fall. You
need someone that's gonna come in and no
matter what position he plays, be
impactful immediately. And I think
there's about seven guys that that can
happen with. Let's be real now. They are
in a position now where they can say,
you know what, we have enough. Let's
move back and get some more picks.
>> Yeah.
>> Thought about that one, you know. So,
anything that they do can be absolutely
Well, and I I love the fact that they've
done that. I know we have a lot of fans
that you have to be a certain player or
not. They don't know what the hell they
talking about. They don't know how to
put a team together. Yeah. So, I'm not
worried about it. If they move back or
if they pick any of the guys we've been
naming, I'm going to be happy with it.
>> Well, it it's a couple of guys in this
draft that I label freaks. All right.
That mean they got a freakish skill set.
Like Jeremiah Love, what he did at that
combine.
>> Sunny
>> Sunny Styles, what he did at that
combine. Sadique, what he did. Like, so
it's like five, four or five guys that
I'm like, I got to get one.
>> Like, I I want to get one of those guys.
and it's seven. I think we in prime real
estate to get one of those guys.
>> You know what I say though? What they
did at the combine is fine. They wearing
t-shirt and panties. I don't care what
they
do when they get on the football field.
Listen, I have seen guys go to the
combine and show up and show out. Then
they get on the football field and they
they can't do anything.
>> Whoever it is,
>> you got to you got to make sure that
that translates from what you did at the
combine, what you did in college, and
bring it to the pros. Whichever one of
those guys that can do that, bring them
for me. I don't care what position they
playing.
>> I think we all agree that combine ain't
nothing but a pillow fight. I we we
totally understand that where you go and
showcase how fast you are and how strong
you are.
>> The pillowcase fight, not even the
pillar inside.
>> So we we totally understand that.
>> B Mitch, I'm not trying to put a guy on
the spot here, but let me flip it on
you. Is there a prospect that you think,
you know what, I keep hearing people
rant and rave about this guy. I'm not
quite sold on him.
Uh, you know what? I've been looking at
a lot of these guys and and I listen, I
can look at it the o other way. I know
one guy people are knocking, but I'm
sold on. Okay. Ruben Bane.
>> Okay.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> Tell me what you want by his his arms
being 1/8 of an inch shorter than
>> Listen, all I know is when he when he
faced people, he beat their ass.
>> Yeah.
>> He he was able to get them off of him.
If his arms were two inches shorter, I
would understand one/8 of an inch.
>> That That's a fingernail. That's a
fingernail.
>> And And let's be be real, you you work
with Fred. Fred coming at some more. He
looks shorter because he hadn't
stretched all THE WAY OUT YET. YOU KNOW,
what if Ruben Bane was to get a little
extra stretch that day? He may have that
exact eighth of an inch, you know. So,
that's I look at it like that. But, you
know, I I think a lot of these guys I
I'm just I'm at a position now where
first in for the first time in in I
would say in the last four or five
years, I look at how receivers and
running backs are using the NFL. And I
think the receiver is more valuable than
the running back. So, when everybody
lose their mind over love, I saw what
he's doing. I know everything that he's
done. But that receiver,
you can go get a receiver like in Tate.
All right. and I think he would probably
be more impactful in a rookie season
than a running back would be.
>> That's hard to That's that's hard coming
from a running back, especially with and
my thing is I think the running back
position has has the biggest glow up to
me in the last three years showing with
Saquon Barkley, Bean Robinson. If you
have a guy that can be a different
maker, it just takes so much pressure
off of the quarterback position. If I
can win on first down, and that's what
running backs do. They win on first
down. And if they can catch out of the
back field on third down, they become
the great equalizer. Cuz when I say
equalizer, as a defensive player, if we
know the running back can catch out of
the back field, we have to be cognizant
of where he at and where he lines up at
all the time.
I agree with you on that. But I'll just
say this, that receiver who's deadly, he
can't be states five yards down the
field.
>> That's a disadvantage for that
secondary. Yeah, we're going to find out
where the commanders go coming up in the
draft. That's our guy, B Mitch. B Mitch,
appreciate you, man. Thank you.
>> All right, ma'am. Y'all take care. Be
cool.
>> Ball head,
let's pay some bills and listen to some
voicemails. Commanders fans, Seekick is
the official primary ticketing partner
of Hail to the Commanders and here to
help you experience all of the action
this season from football to funk and
any other live events at Northwest
Stadium, SeatGeek. Our good friends at
SeatGeek, they have all the tickets.
Seek the official primary ticketing
partner of the Washington Commanders and
Northwest Stadium. What about Virginia
Lottery? Huddle up Commanders fans. The
Commanders Golden Pass Raffle operated
by the Virginia Lottery gives you the
chance to win the ultimate fan
experience. That means tickets, VIP
treatment. Special appearances by
Washington Legends and so much more.
Limited tickets are available. So visit
vaottery.com/commanders
to enter the raffle today. That is
vaulty.com/commanders
and break.
>> Nice.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> Listen, did you watch the Oscars?
>> Did you? I I just have to ask.
>> I thought Swift's going to give me a
compliment here. He goes,
>> "Hey, man. Did you watch the Oscars?"
>> I just got
>> I watched a lot of the Oscars. Yes.
>> Did you really? I All I'm saying is
this. sinners for all the all the ones
that they won.
>> They could have won more, right? They
could have still won more.
>> It's never enough.
>> All I'm saying is this. The story of
Fred Smoot, which will be told probably
like 40 years from now,
>> right?
>> Michael B. Jordan.
>> That'll probably be called Sinners TOO.
>> YEAH.
>> YES. Played by Michael B. JORDAN.
>> MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
>> LISTEN, cut the mustache off Michael and
play Fred Smooth. All right. IT WOULDN'T
BE HARD. THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> There's so many things I WANT TO SAY. SO
MANY.
>> Let me ask you this.
>> The story of Michael Jenkins. Who plays
Michael Jenkins?
>> Oh, probably like Martin Short,
you know,
>> cuz you didn't heard the Martin Short.
>> I've heard that. I've heard Conan. I've
heard that.
>> Conan could really play you.
>> Yeah.
>> Like Conan.
>> I've gotten that a few times. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I think more Michael B. Jordan for
me. Maybe, you know, Denzel. Vince's
always a good choice.
>> Yeah, you know, I'm just saying.
>> Let's talk to our favorite St. Patty's
Day producer. There she is in her green.
Anna's here.
>> Yes, Anna.
>> That's my St. Patrick's Day.
>> Welcome back.
>> Will G. Willer.
>> Well, I was First of all, I was going to
say last week on the podcast, we talked
about barbecue and as some of you know,
I had a brutal trip back, but um as a
result, capitalized on the opportunity.
I revived Logan's Twitter a little bit.
So, if you all want me to continue the
Q&A,
>> was that you yesterday?
>> Well, yes, but but but I wasn't
answering for Logan for the record. I
just would type his responses for
>> He was basically his secretary.
>> He was on a roll yesterday. I was like,
>> "Yeah, he was on a roll. That was two
hours of two hours on the airplane. Anna
was bored." But, um, when we were coming
back from Austin, I finally got to have
quality barbecue. And I get it now. I
understand. I never understood barbecue
like all the rage. Like, I get it now.
And So, so now you ready to stand by
that Texas is the best American barbecue
>> as of now? Yes. My mind could be
changed. I'm open to trying other
>> Mississippi.
Yeah. Maybe next time I if I ever end up
in Mississippi one of these days
>> once you reach the summit, you know,
>> ain't no going back down on my
>> Why would I go eat North Carolina
barbecue when I have Texas? I have said
like remember I feel like last year we
talked a little bit about how we have my
friends and I have a grill and all we've
really done are hot dogs on it. I
understand why people are so passionate
about barbecue now and why that's a
little insulting and I apologize
>> cuz it's it's the the time the smoking
of it. The smoking is how much patience
do you have?
>> Right.
>> That's exactly right.
>> That's what barbecue is.
>> Yeah. Well,
>> without further ado, shall we get into
our voicemails? Let's do it.
>> Let's do it.
Thanks. Anna, what's happening? What's
happening? What's happening?
Hey, AP is cooking. That boy is cooking.
Yes.
Lord have mercy. He cooking. Hey, look.
I got a draft question for you guys,
man. If you got the option between
Jeremiah Love, Caleb Dal, and Sunny
Styles, who you kicking at seven. All
right. Now, if you pass up on Jeremiah
Love, what's the plan at running back
based on the draft and who's available?
>> I would go with Love.
>> Okay.
>> So, you would go Love.
>> You know, I've thought about it a lot. I
mean, all three of those guys are dudes.
>> Yeah.
>> But
look, the current running back room is
four guys on one-year contracts, and
they don't have anybody like him. And I
really think imagine a guy that dynamic
at running back could really unlock
things for Jaden as well and the rest of
that offense. For any other running
back, absolutely not.
>> Yeah.
>> But I think AP did a good enough job, a
very good, not a very good enough job,
but a good enough job on defense of
addressing
>> all three lines of the defense, all
three sections of the defense where you
can afford to go to the running back
here.
>> You know, I'm a Sunny Styles. Listen,
Sunny Styles just does it.
>> How's it going?
>> Listen to me. Just Oh my god. Now is the
team
is built now after free agency.
>> Mhm. Leo Chanel and those guys have
given me put like this.
I love Dollar Bill. I think Dollar Bill
is a starting running back in this
league,
>> but every three, four years, we have
this Saquon or this Bejon or this
Christian McCaffrey or this this dude,
someone who's special.
>> And that what I said like if I'm taking
you in the top 10, you got to have the F
word beside you. Freakish talent.
>> Oh,
>> freakish talent.
>> All right. Like if I'm taking you in the
top 10.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. And let's go through these.
Out of the three you named, Caleb DS,
uh, Sunonny Styles, Jeremiah Love, two
are freaks. Mhm. Two skill sets are
nothing like anybody else in this draft.
So, I would probably agree with you and
go Jeremiah Love only because it
instantly makes the offense
potent.
>> Yes.
>> Like lethal,
>> right? Like we have a lethal passer, a
lethal runner, and a lethal catcher, and
a lethal left tackle. Lethal. All right.
That means illegal in most states.
Lethal. All right. So,
Sunny Styles on the defense. Does that
make this linebacking court lethal? I
think it does.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But
>> nasty. But boy, Jeremiah love Jay and
Jay is what they'll probably call them.
>> And also
>> Jaden and Jeremiah that running back
room and then you got White catching
passes out of the back field. Bill
always a home run threatening spots. I
mean situationally you could do a lot.
>> It just I it's a play caller's dream. M
>> if I'm the offensive coordinator, all
I'm sitting there is please like draft
him because how easy is it to call the
first round I mean a first first down
run right
>> with him in there. All right. What about
the pass run option with these two?
Yeah. And don't forget Jeremiah Love
soft hands sponsored by Pampers. All
right. All I'm saying is
>> it could make the offense almost
unstoppable. I don't disagree. We're in
agreement.
>> All right. Next. Next. Voicemail.
>> What is up, Anna Jin?
This is Mitch from Richmond.
>> Mitch from Richmond.
>> Today is uh
March 12th. The free agency is running
hot right now. And I'm listening to B
Mitch and Finley and and you know I'm
listening to Grant and Danny and and
Rock on Commanders and all that stuff
with Logan. And I tell you what, there
are some fans right now who are just
like way out of line. For one, if you're
not a professional football player,
don't be saying players suck because
they're damn sure better than you.
>> Thank you. Another thing is, why are you
so angry about Adam Peter signing a
bunch of people? Man, you they're
knocking it out of the park. I I'm
ecstatic with what they're doing right
now. They're pulling all kinds of people
in, and it's quite apparent that they
are making an effort to approve this
team. But guess what? As a fan, and I've
been a fan since 83,
I don't care who they signed. I don't
care. I'm still gonna love this team
unconditionally and I'm still gonna
watch every single game until the clock
says zero. Win or lose, I don't care.
I'm a Commander fan. I'm a football team
fan. I'm a Redskins fan. I'm just a
Burgundy and Gold fan. And it's always
going to be that way. So, people just
need to chill out, enjoy the team, enjoy
Easter football,
and don't go on some emotional roller
coaster that you have no control over.
Pointless.
Very, very pointless. You know, like I
like like let's say I call cell phone
towers for a living. I work in
telecommunications.
Well, guess what? Guess what I don't do.
I don't work in the NFL. So, who would I
be to say that someone talks until the
day that one of these players try to
climb a tower and I got something to
show them? But I'm gonna keep my mouth
shut. Just love this team. I appreciate
everything you guys do. You all have a
great day. Bye-bye.
>> Thank you, man. Listen, that's one of my
pet peeves because I love sports talk
radio, okay?
>> But it it's so cringy to hear these
dudes, these unafetic dudes call dudes
on the roster sorry. First of all, you
couldn't play with none of them,
>> right? But isn't there a difference?
Because this is where this is where I
think it's interesting. I don't believe
that you have to have played a
professional sport to know the sport.
No, I don't think that
>> there is a difference between that and
being educated about any sport,
including NFL, and then deciding, "Oh,
you suck. You can't play." Like, that's
a different line.
>> It's a respect line.
>> Yes. Like, when I hear some of these
dudes be like, "Oh, oh, boy is a Jag."
And I'm like,
>> "You don't have the right to call him a
Jag, right?
>> You ain't earned the right to call him a
Jag. What's your athletic prowess?"
Right?
>> Like, that's where I think the class
comes in at. the class comes in at with
the lack of respect.
>> Yeah.
>> Like it's I can hear this from uh dudes
all the time. They can take it from a
former athlete. They can really take it
from a former athlete. They be like,
"All right, whatever."
>> But when they hear it from somebody that
did not it just rip it does something to
them like not you. You can't you can't
say that.
>> You cannot say that. And I hear it all
the time. I hear it all the time when
I'm listening and I be like, "That's
just total disrespect because the last
man on the last roster in the NFL is
part of a 1% that 99% of the world is
not." That's exactly right.
>> And just because he might not be the
best of that 1%, the 1% that he's a part
of is already
athletically dominant than the other
part.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I think that's what kind of rubs NFL
players the wrong way. And that's why
NFL players do not listen to sports
talk.
>> Yeah.
>> While we're playing, we do not listen to
sports talk radio.
>> And I also think too, if you're talking
about AP, the key is, and of course,
sometimes there's a superstar, can't
miss, already proven it.
>> Those are the guys that get the biggest
money. Yeah.
>> But the real key, especially when you
have a lot of cap space, is to take guys
who are right there on the precipice
>> of being who they going to be,
>> of being who they're going to be, and
being in their prime. like Oay, like
Chson, each had seven and a half sacks
last year, like Chanel, who is
aggressive, who can play all over the
place, who has two Super Bowls. So,
you're bringing in guys where
>> it might seem like, okay, maybe you're
overpaying in spots, but also these guys
could explode, and you're getting a lot
of value.
>> First of all, let me tell people about
free agency. Free agency is classic o
overpaying. I when people are bidding on
you, THE PRICE GOES UP,
>> RIGHT? SO IF IT STARTED at 10 million,
by the time we finish bidding, it's
going to be at 17 million. Am I playing
overpric? Am I paying overly for this?
YES. BECAUSE IT was a bidding war. When
it like if I'm if it's in house and the
only person we bidding against IS
OURSELF, THE PRICE DOESN'T SKYROCKET,
RIGHT?
>> WE ALREADY TELLING YOU WHERE THE PRICE
IS AT. But when you're a free agent,
it's classic overpaying. We see it all
the time. That's why we love to get to
free agency. PLAYERS.
>> YEAH,
>> CUZ WE'RE ABOUT TO GET OVER BIDDED ON.
LIKE I KNOW DEEP down I'm only worth 10,
but they about to give me 20. WHO CARES,
>> RIGHT?
>> NOBODY. LIKE, so anytime free agency and
people say overpay, I say no, ain't no
such thing as overpay. It's how many
more dollars do I need to pay you than
what they said they going to give you?
That's all it's about. And once you get
into a bid war Yes. like any other thing
that you purchase through a bid, it's
going to be overpriced.
>> Yeah. All right, Anna.
>> All right, last voicemail. We'll hit
maybe one more email and then we'll be
good.
>> Okay.
>> Hey, Fred and Jens. So, and Anna, Mike,
I'll be quick this time, but I'm
finishing the podcast. And uh Freddy,
I'm sorry, but I have to disagree with
you. Uh you mentioned uh Josh Allen and
Lamar Jackson in the playoffs. They've
missed. I put it on those two. I say
Jaden's better because Jaden can make
the big throw. I don't think when the
chips are down, when it's deep, and I've
seen it time and time again with Lamar
and Josh Allen, they choke. I'm sorry.
They're they're they're when they have
to make they've missed when guys have
been wide open. So, and yes, I know that
tight end dropped poor guy
and he closes his eyes at night and his
head hits the pillow. I know. And life's
tough. Money's not everything. So, it
doesn't hurt though, right? But
seriously, that's why I say Jaden's
better than Josh Allen and Lamar Jackson
because he can make the big throw. Those
two have missed the big throw quite a
bit. Quite a bit when they needed to
make it. Just my opinion. I know it's
harsh, but I'm a harsh fan. And uh I
also think, you know, uh and like many
of us uh Washington fans that uh um his
rookie year, JD5 should have been um
Jedi 5. All right. You happy? Should
have been in contention for MVP because
it was an MVP season. It was the best
rookie season in the history of of uh
quarterbacks. You know, maybe slinging
Sammy was there. I love it. Slick and
Sammy. But anyway, I I beg to differ
again. Who am I? Who am I to call those
two guys chokers? But I'm just saying
it's a game of inches and it's, you
know, it's a hairline. But again,
I I I put
I that's that's what I think makes Jaden
better. That's why I think we can come
storming back and get in the Super Bowl
and actually beat Philly because of
Jaden. Uh, anyway, that's my two cents.
I took a little longer than expected.
Big surprise. Later, fellas. God bless.
>> I love it that he cracks himself up cuz
you got to be really entertaining to
yourself to make yourself laugh like
that.
>> As as much we love Jaden, though.
>> Yeah.
>> You putting him above Lamar and Josh
Allen.
>> This is what he's saying is in the skill
set of throwing because that's what he
was talking about.
He's saying that he felt like Jaden had
a little bit more touch and clutch.
>> Okay.
>> Clutch where he's saying
only knock on Lamar.
>> Mhm.
>> Is they haven't been clutch during the
clutch time, right? But I would fight
that back and say Mark Andrews dropped
that pass.
>> Josh Allen has not been responsible for
those. I mean, how many times is he
running to the Chiefs? Look, does Jaden
have that potential?
>> Yes.
>> No question about it. But it's hard for
me to say
>> he's better than
>> objectively. Look, you're talking about
three MVPs total, right? Two for Lamar
and one for Josh Allen.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. So,
>> I love Jaden like everybody else. But at
some point, you know, you can't one
playoff run is hard for me to measure
against multiple NBA multiple playoffs.
It's just it's just different on that
one. Like, here go the thing about it.
our guy just getting started. These guys
trying to get over the hump,
>> right? All right. They trying to get
over the hump. And one hump was named
Patrick Mahome. All right. And that was
a big hump that most people couldn't get
past.
>> Right.
>> So, no, I don't It's just hard, man.
Like, they're going to think about
quarterback. They get all the love for
the wins, but they also get all the the
hate for the losses,
>> right?
>> So, you know, it's a it's a win lose
thing right there.
>> Well, wow. We have one more email. It's
fine though. Oh,
>> okay. It's from our friend Omare, winner
of the Segeek um challenge.
Congratulations. Shout out. Shout out
Omare. Congrats again. And thank you to
Segeek for always letting us do such fun
things. All that stuff. All right. From
Hello, Anna Jinx, Kayla Smoot. As
someone who loves Commander YouTube
channel and hopes it carries on forever,
who do you see on the roster that could
carry the torch onto the next phase of
weekly shows? As a command center super
fan, I would personally think Santana
would be succeeded by Terry, Logan, John
Bates, and Tim Settle could fill the
Fred role, although no one could truly
live up to him. And he gave his reasons
why. Um I I know no, nobody wants to let
their backup start, but if you think who
do you think could, you know,
>> fill the gap in for me?
>> Yeah.
>> All right.
>> They're already trying to put you out
the pack.
>> Yes, I been put out the
>> Fred, you talked about retiring from the
NFL. When you retire from Get Loud
>> and the rest of the show anytime who All
right, let's go personalities.
>> I'm thinking like it's got to be a DV.
It's got to be
>> Well, person DBs usually have the
personality,
>> right?
>> But it got to be some mainstay in there.
It can't be a guy that got a cup of
coffee with the team. It It has to be
somebody with some some peps on the
wall. When it comes to the team,
>> you think of him as a commander.
>> Yes. When you think of this dude, you
have to think of him as a commander. And
the one position that we've always got
right is cornerback. And we continue to
do that. I think Mikey going to continue
with that going.
>> Who could take my place? They got to be
edgy, live funny,
>> sexy.
>> Got to be sexy.
>> All right. Uh, who you think?
>> I don't know cuz I
>> I'm trying to rag my brain, but I don't
know. Who you got, Anna?
>> I think somebody who's like funny, big
personality. Jeremy Reeves. And he's
been here a long he's been here through
stuff.
>> Revo is a good one.
>> That is a good one.
>> Revo is a good one. Like I have to say
Revo, but I'm going to blow everybody
away.
>> Trey Amos.
>> No. Tres way.
Tres way.
>> Tres would be great.
>> Tres would be great
>> would be the guy.
>> He has a great personality.
>> Great personality. Great energy. And the
punter never gets time to talk.
>> That's true.
>> All right. So, I would say Tres Wade for
me
>> for Santana.
I don't know if it'll be Terry cuz Terry
do has a great personality
>> and John Bates. John actually had a very
good personality when we uh talked to
him.
>> Yeah.
>> Him and Logan kind of the same dude,
ain't it? Also too, it's interesting too
is some of these athletes where they
start off and once they get a little
more comfortable.
>> Yeah.
>> Then they open up even more like they
would in a locker room or in a setting
with their friends.
>> See, just think about it. Unless you in
the locker room
>> Yeah.
>> you don't truly know who's who.
>> Cuz like Tanner was a little bit
reserved.
>> No, no, a little bit.
>> I mean, he was right.
>> Tanner was very quiet.
>> Reserved. And now when you see him, I
mean, he's great.
>> Now he just We can't get him.
>> He got a little more. He got more
comfortable and it's like, "Oh, you're
seeing the Tanner that you normally
see."
>> Yeah. So, yeah. So, it's about
development and who opens up. Yeah, but
it's hard to replace us now.
>> You're not retiring.
>> Yeah, I'm never going to retire ever.
>> I'm dying to see.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> Carry me out.
>> The first time I retired really did
something to me. It really just rubbed
me the wrong way. I said never again.
>> What are we doing for the draft? I see a
little tease here. We have our plans yet
for the draft? We don't know.
>> Oh, you mean in terms of like
>> our coverage?
Oh,
>> get loud. Draft party preview.
>> There might be a little there.
>> Is that a tease?
>> That that was maybe going to be
discussed, but we're gonna we're gonna
keep that a little secret for now. But
just
>> draft party preview. I don't know.
>> Just know there's there's something's
cooking up.
>> Hey, AP ain't the only one cooking.
>> All right, we'll let you know. So, we
got something. You know, we're going to
do something
anyway. So, we'll let you know. It's
okay. Figure it out. That's it for the
end of the podcast cuz I'm a seat geek.
Mhm.
>> By the time they pull you out of that
chair, that leather's going to be mold
around your butt. Listen, 193 years old.
>> The Get Loud podcast was filmed at the
Big Bear AI Command Center Studios. Big
Bear AI offers mission ready AI for
rapidly evolving world and proudly
protecting the Washington Commanders and
his fans.
The views and opinions expressed by our
podcast guests and/or hosts are their
own and do not necessarily reflect the
views or positions of the Washington
commanders or any of their
representatives.